RG 005:034, Office of the Governor: John Dempsey (1961-1971)
Connecticut State Library
- Series 11. Speeches with related materials, 1961-1970
  - Main Files, 1961-1970
    - Governor in Action Program (League of Women Voters), 1962 (Box A-420)
    - National Governors Conference, Advisory Committee on Federal-State Local Relations, 1967 (Box A-420)
    - National Governors Conference, Gun Control Legislation, 1968 (Box A-420)
    - Governors Conference on Children and Youth, 1966 (Box A-420)
    - Governors Conference on Children and Youth, 1964 (Box A-420)
    - Governors Conference on Children and Youth, 1962 (Box A-420)
    - Governors Conference on Emergency Resources Management, 1964 (Box A-420)
    - Governors Conference on Human Rights and Opportunities, 1967 (Box A-420)
    - Governors Conference on Human Rights and Opportunities, Closing Remarks, 1967 (Box A-420)
    - Governors Conference on Interregional Planning, Hartford, 1964 (Box A-420)
    - Governors Conference on Natural and Environmental Beauty, 1966 (Box A-420)
    - Governors Conference on Recreation, Hartford, 1969 (Box A-420)
    - Governors Conference on Recreation, Hartford, 1968 (Box A-420)
    - Governors Conference on Recreation, 1967 November 1 (Box A-420)
    - Governors Conference on Recreation, 7th Annual Meeting, 1966 (Box A-420)
    - Governors Conference on Recreation, Hartford, 1965 (Box A-420)
    - Governors Conference on Recreation, Hartford, 1964 (Box A-420)
    - Governors Conference on Recreation, Hartford, 1963 (Box A-420)
    - Governors Conference on Recreation, Hartford, 1962 (Box A-420)
    - Governors Conference on Recreation, Hartford, 1961 (Box A-420)
    - Governors Conference, Transportation Workshop, Hershey, Pennsylvania, 1962 (Box A-420)
    - Governor's Foot Guard 1st Company 195th Anniversary, Hartford, 1966 (Box A-420)
    - Governor's Horse Guard 1st Company, 1966 (Box A-420)
    - 9th Annual Governor's Prayer Breakfast, Hartford, 1970 (Box A-420)
    - Governor's Prayer Breakfast, Hartford, 1969 (Box A-420)
    - Governor's Prayer Breakfast, 1968 (Box A-420)
    - Governor's Prayer Breakfast, 6th Annual, Hartford, 1967 (Box A-420)
    - Governor's Prayer Breakfast, Hartford, 1966 (Box A-420)
    - Governor's Prayer Breakfast, Hartford, 1965 (Box A-420)
    - Governor's Prayer Breakfast, Hartford, 1964 (Box A-420)
    - Governor's Prayer Breakfast, Providence, Rhode Island, 1965 (Box A-420)
    - Governors Traffic Safety Conference, Central Conn. State College, 1966 (Box A-420)
    - Grange, State Convention, Foot Guard Hall, Hartford, 1966 (Box A-420)
    - Grange, State Convention, 1965 (Box A-421)
    - Grange - Enfield Grange No. 151, Hazardville, 1966 (Box A-421)
    - Grasso, Ella, Award of Order of Italy, Hartford Hilton, 1968 (Box A-421)
    - Greater Hartford Council on Economic Education, Norwich, 1961 (Box A-421)
    - Greater Hartford Forum, Bloomfield, 1964 (Box A-421)
    - Greater Hartford Jaycees Outstanding Boss Award, Hartford Hilton Hotel, Lt. Gov. Attilio Frassinelli, 1968 (Box A-421)
    - Greenwich Safety Council Grand Award Presentation Luncheon, Greenwich, 1965 (Box A-421)
    - Greenwich United Nations Day Celebration, 1966 (Box A-421)
    - Griswold, Town of, 150th Anniversary, 1965 (Box A-421)
    - Groton, Opening of Access Highway, 1966 (Box A-421)
    - Guilford, Civil War Centennial Commission Celebration, 1965 (Box A-421)
    - Hall Meadow Brook Dam & Reservoir Dedication, Torrington, 1962 (Box A-421)
    - Hall Meadow Brook Dam, Torrington, 1961 (Box A-421)
    - Hamden Chamber of Commerce Annual Meeting, 1966 (Box A-421)
    - Hamden Democratic Town Committee Women's Group, 1962 (Box A-421)
    - Greater Hartford Chamber of Commerce Legislative Dinner, Lt. Gov. Attilio Frassinelli, 1969 (Box A-421)
    - Greater Hartford Chamber of Commerce Annual Meeting, 1968 (Box A-421)
    - Greater Hartford Chamber of Commerce Banquet, 1962 (Box A-421)
    - Greater Hartford Chamber of Commerce, 1961 (Box A-421)
    - Greater Hartford Community College Commencement, Traveler's Insurance Co., Hartford, 1969 (Box A-421)
    - Hartford College for Women, Commencement, 1967 (Box A-421)
    - Hartford College, Father's Club, 1966 (Box A-421)
    - Hartford Courant Anniversary Dinner, 1964 (Box A-421)
    - Hartford Democratic Town Committee "Meet the Candidates" Dance, 1967 (Box A-421)
    - Hartford Education Association Forum, Hartford, 1966 (Box A-421)
    - Hartford Housing Project - Dedication of Mary Hannan Mahoney Village, 1963 (Box A-421)
    - Hartford High School Assembly, Thomas J. Quirk Award, 1961 (Box A-421)
    - Hartford Chamber of Commerce Dinner, 1962 (Box A-421)
    - Dedication - Hartford National Bank, 1967 (Box A-421)
    - Hartford Times 150th Anniversary Dinner, 1967 (Box A-421)
    - Harkness Memorial Park, 1968 (Box A-421)
    - Health Directors Cedarcrest Hospital, 1963 (Box A-421)
    - Hibernians, Ancient Order of, Anniversary Dinner and Dance, 1965 (Box A-421)
    - Highway Users Conference, Hartford, 1965 (Box A-421)
    - Holy Family Layman's Retreat, Waterbury Chapter, 1966 (Box A-421)
    - Holy Innocents Guild, Second Annual Dinner Dance, 1962 (Box A-421)
    - Speech - Home Builders Association of Hartford County, 1962 (Box A-421)
    - Home Fallout Civil Defense, State Capitol, 1968 June 11 (Box A-421)
    - Hotel America Opening Ceremonies, Hartford, 1964 (Box A-421)
    - Housing and Redevelopment Officials Conference, 1962 (Box A-421)
    - Speech - Housing and Redevelopment, Conn. Association of, 1961 (Box A-421)
    - Housing and Redevelopment Conference, 1968 (Box A-421)
    - Commission on Human Rights and Opportunities, 25th Anniversary Dinner, Hartford, 1968 (Box A-421)
    - Vice President Hubert Humphrey Introductory Remarks, 1968 (Box A-421)
    - Lenten Worship Service Immanuel Lutheran Church, Meriden, 1968 (Box A-421)
    - Industrial Management Club "Top Management Night", 1962 (Box A-421)
    - Industrial Management - Joint Meeting of Norwich and New London Clubs, 1962 (Box A-421)
    - Industrial Management Club, 1966 (Box A-421)
    - Ingraham Company, Cornerstone Laying Ceremony, Bristol, 1964 (Box A-421)
    - Insurance Luncheon, 1961 (Box A-421)
    - Insurers National Association of Independent, 1964 (Box A-421)
    - Intercollegiate Legislature Opening, 1968 (Box A-421)
    - Conn. Intercollegiate Student Legislature, 1965 (Box A-421)
    - Conn. Intercollegiate Student Legislature, 1962 (Box A-421)
    - Interstate Commerce Committee, 1965 (Box A-421)
    - Interstate Highway No. 91, Meriden-New Haven Section, 1966 (Box A-421)
    - Interstate Route 91, Rocky Hill Dedication Ceremonies, 1964 (Box A-421)
    - Interstate 95 (Groton), 1964 (Box A-421)
    - 25th Anniversary Dinner, Irish American Home Society, Glastonbury, 1970 (Box A-421)
    - Irish American Home Society Dinner, 1967 December 7 (Box A-421)
    - Italian Migration, American Committee on, Annual Meeting, 1966 (Box A-421)
    - Italian Prime Minister Aldo Moro and Minister of Foreign Affairs, Fanfani, New York, 1965 (Box A-421)
    - New York - Dinner Honoring President Segni of Italy, 1964 (Box A-421)
    - Association of Investment Brokers, Hartford Chapter, 1967 (Box A-421)
    - Japan, Northeast States Conference on Exports, 1965 (Box A-421)
    - Jaysea House Opening Ceremonies, New London, 1968 (Box A-421)
    - Jefferson Jackson Day, Statement of John Bailey, 1970 (Box A-421)
    - Jefferson Jackson Day Dinner, 1970 (Box A-422)
    - Jefferson Jackson Day Dinner, 1969 (Box A-422)
    - Jefferson Jackson Day Dinner, 1968 (Box A-422)
    - Jefferson Jackson Day Dinner, 1967 (Box A-422)
    - Jefferson Jackson Day Dinner, 1966 (Box A-422)
    - Jefferson Jackson Day Dinner, 1965 (Box A-422)
    - Jefferson Jackson Day Dinner, 1964 (Box A-422)
    - Jefferson Jackson Day Dinner, 1963 (Box A-422)
    - Jefferson Jackson Day Dinner, 1962 (Box A-422)
    - Jefferson Jackson Day Dinner, 1961 (Box A-422)
    - Junior Achievement, 1965 (Box A-422)
    - Kent Center School Graduation, 1962 (Box A-422)
    - Killian, Robert, 1965 (Box A-422)
    - Killingly High School Graduation Exercises, 1965 (Box A-422)
    - David C. King Award (Conn. Society of Gerontology), 1963 (Box A-422)
    - King, Dr. Martin Luther, 1966 (Box A-422)
    - King, Dr. Martin Luther, Mt. Olive Baptist Church Program, 1964 (Box A-422)
    - Martin Luther King Freedom Rally, 1962 (Box A-422)
    - Kiwannis, New England District Convention, 1961 (Box A-422)
    - Knights of Columbus, Dedication, New Haven, 1969 (Box A-422)
    - Knights of Columbus, Clergy Appreciation Night, Norwich, 1963 (Box A-422)
    - Knights of Columbus Scholarship Dinner, 1962 (Box A-422)
    - Knights of Columbus, 1965 (Box A-422)
    - Knox Glass, Inc., Opening New Plant, Danielson, 1966 (Box A-422)
    - Knox Glass, Ground Breaking Ceremony, Danielson, 1964 (Box A-422)
    - Herman P. Koppleman Award Dinner, Emanuel Synagogue, West Hartford, 1967 (Box A-422)
    - Conn. State Labor Council, 1967 (Box A-422)
    - Conn. State Labor Council, 1961 (Box A-422)
    - Labor Council Convention, 1962 (Box A-422)
    - Labor Council Convention, 1963 (Box A-422)
    - Labor Council Convention, Bridgeport, 1964 (Box A-422)
    - Labor Council Convention, State, 1965 (Box A-422)
    - Labor Council, State, Annual Convention, 1966 (Box A-422)
    - Labor Relations Agencies, National Association of, 1965 (Box A-422)
    - Lane Bryant Awards, 1965 (Box A-422)
    - Laurel Club, 1969 (Box A-422)
    - Law Day, 1962 (Box A-422)
    - Lions Clubs Conference, 1962 (Box A-422)
    - Litchfield County Federated Democratic Women's Clubs, Torrington, 1962 (Box A-422)
    - Lithuanian-American Citizens Club, Hartford, 1964 (Box A-422)
    - Lithuanian-American Community of the USA, 1966 (Box A-422)
    - Lithuanian Independence Day Meeting, Hartford, 1968 (Box A-422)
    - Long Lane School Dedication, 1961 (Box A-422)
    - Loyalty Day Program, Norwalk, 1961 (Box A-422)
    - Macy's, Opening of New Store, New Haven, 1964 (Box A-422)
    - Making the Most of Maturity Second Anniversary, 1967 (Box A-422)
    - Mallory Battery Co. Dedication Waterbury, 1968 (Box A-422)
    - Manchester Chamber of Commerce, Meeting, 1964 (Box A-422)
    - Manchester, West Hill Gardens Addition, 1966 (Box A-422)
    - West Hill Gardens, Dedication Manchester, 1962 (Box A-422)
    - Mansfield Program, 1970 (Box A-422)
    - Mansfield State Training School and Hospital, Dedication of Bennett Hall, 1964 (Box A-422)
    - Manson Laboratories - Wilton, Dedication of New Plant, 1964 (Box A-422)
    - Conn. Manufacturers Association Annual Dinner, 1970 (Box A-422)
    - Manufacturers Association of Conn. 151st Annual Meeting, Yale University, 1966 (Box A-422)
    - Manufacturers Association of Conn., Middletown, 1965 (Box A-422)
    - Manufacturers Association of Conn., 1963 (Box A-422)
    - Manufacturers Association of Conn., 1965 (Box A-422)
    - Manufacturers Association of Conn., 1962 (Box A-422)
    - Manufacturers Association of Hartford County, 1965 (Box A-422)
    - Manufacturers Association of Conn. Annual Meeting, 1964 (Box A-422)
    - Marine Corps, U.S. (Nutmeg Platoon), 1964 (Box A-422)
    - Marine Corps League, 1964 (Box A-422)
    - Marianapolis Preparatory School Commencement Address, 1969 (Box A-422)
    - Maronite Day in Conn., 1966 (Box A-422)
    - Media and Minorities Conference, University of Hartford, 1968 (Box A-422)
    - Contract Signing Conn.-New York Modernization Program, 1970 (Box A-422)
    - Signing of Memorandum of Intent for Conn.-New York Commuter Rail Modernization Program, 1969 (Box A-422)
    - Memorial Day Service, 1961 (Box A-422)
    - Memorial Day Service, 1963 (Box A-422)
    - Memorial Day Service, 1964 (Box A-423)
    - Memorial Day Service, 1965 (Box A-423)
    - Memorial Day Service, Conn. State Employees, 1966 (Box A-423)
    - Memorial Day Service, 1967 (Box A-423)
    - Memorial Day Service, 1968 (Box A-423)
    - Memorial Day Service, 1968 (Box A-423)
    - Memorial Day Service, 1970 (Box A-423)
    - Memorial Day Service, 1969 (Box A-423)
    - Memorial Day, West Hartford, 1959 (Box A-423)
    - Mental Deficiency, American Association on, 1963 (Box A-423)
    - Mental Health Council, Middlesex Area, 1965 (Box A-423)
    - Mental Health, 1965 (Box A-423)
    - Mental Health Center, New Haven, 1966 (Box A-423)
    - Mental Health Center, Conn., Ground Breaking Program, 1964 (Box A-423)
    - Mental Health, Conn. Association for, Annual Meeting, 1964 (Box A-423)
    - Mental Health, Dedication of the Franklin S. DuBois Day Treatment Center, Stamford, 1964 (Box A-423)
    - Mental Health Congress, Conn., Aetna Life Insurance Co., 1965 (Box A-423)
    - Mental Health, Northeast State Government Conference, 1964 (Box A-423)
    - Mental Retardation Planning Committee, 1966 (Box A-423)
    - Mental Retardation Planning, 1964 (Box A-423)
    - Mentally Retarded Annual Convention of Association for Retarded Children, 1965 (Box A-423)
    - Greater Hartford Center for the Mentally Retarded, 1966 (Box A-423)
    - Mentally Retarded, Greater Hartford Center for, 1965 (Box A-423)
    - Mentally Retarded, Conn. Special Olympics, UConn. Athletic Field, 1969 (Box A-423)
    - Mentally Retarded, New Haven Regional Center, 1966 (Box A-423)
    - New Haven Regional Center for the Mentally Retarded, 1964 (Box A-423)
    - Meriden Chamber of Commerce, Waverly Inn, Cheshire, 1962 (Box A-423)
    - Meriden - Willow Court Housing Project, 1964 (Box A-423)
    - Methodist Youth Fellowship Rally, 1964 (Box A-423)
    - Metropolitan Regional Council Law Enforcement Committee, 1965 (Box A-423)
    - Middlebury Democratic Town Committee Annual Dinner, 1962 (Box A-423)
    - Middlesex Community College Convocation, 1966 (Box A-423)
    - Lewis S. Mills Regional High School, Burlington, 1961 (Box A-423)
    - Thursday Ministers Club, 1961 (Box A-423)
    - Thursday Ministers Group, 1962 (Box A-423)
    - Thursday Ministers Group, 1963 (Box A-423)
    - Ministers Fellowship of Hartford, Asylum Hill Congregational Church, 1966 (Box A-423)
    - Mohegan Pequot Bridge, Montville, Dedication, 1967 (Box A-423)
    - Montville Vietnam Monument Dedication, Montville, 1969 (Box A-423)
    - James H. Moran Jr. High School, Wallingford, Dedication, 1962 (Box A-423)
    - William Mortensen Luncheon, 1968 (Box A-423)
    - Dedication of Moses Wheeler Bridge, Milford, 1962 (Box A-423)
    - Senator Edmund Muskie Campaign Speech, 1968 (Box A-423)
    - U.S.S. Nathan Hale, New London, 1968 (Box A-423)
    - Nathan Hale Submarine Dedication Ceremony (speech not given), 1963 (Box A-423)
    - National Alliance of Business Men, 1969 (Box A-423)
    - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People Centennial Celebration, Hartford, 1963 (Box A-423)
    - National Conference of Christians and Jews 40th Banquet, 1968 (Box A-423)
    - National Conference of Christians and Jews 38th Annual Banquet, 1966 (Box A-423)
    - National Governors Conference, Lake of the Ozarks, 1970 (Box A-423)
    - National Governors Conference, Rural and Urban Development, 1970 (Box A-423)
    - National Governors Conference, Gun Control Legislation, 1968 (Box A-423)
    - National Order of Women Legislators 29th Convention, 1967 (Box A-423)
    - National Safety Council Banquet, 1961 (Box A-423)
    - National Governors Conference, Colorado Springs, 1969 (Box A-423)
    - National Science Teachers Association, New England Regional Conference, 1966 (Box A-423)
    - Natural Resources Council of Conn., 1966 (Box A-423)
    - Natural Resources Council 13th Annual Conference, 1962 (Box A-423)
    - Naugatuck News - Dedication of New Plant, 1965 (Box A-423)
    - Naugatuck Valley Chamber of Commerce, Lower Ansonia, 1965 (Box A-423)
    - New Britain Chamber of Commerce, 1966 (Box A-423)
    - New England Association of Circulation Managers, 1963 (Box A-423)
    - New England Associated Press Managing Editors' Association, 1966 (Box A-423)
    - New England Press Association, Boston, 1966 (Box A-423)
    - New England Council Conn. Dinner, 1967 (Box A-423)
    - New England Council Conn. State Dinner, 1965 (Box A-424)
    - New England Governors Conference, 1969 (Box A-424)
    - New England Interstate Water Pollution Commission, 1966 (Box A-424)
    - New England Council Seminar, New England's Economic Development Trends, 1966 (Box A-424)
    - New England Regional Commission Public Hearings, State Capitol, 1967 (Box A-424)
    - New England Society in the City of New York, 1966 (Box A-424)
    - New Haven Crawford Manor, 1966 (Box A-424)
    - New Haven Chamber of Commerce, 1966 (Box A-424)
    - New Haven Community Jewish Center, 1965 (Box A-424)
    - New Haven Club of Providence College, 1964 (Box A-424)
    - New Haven Citizens" Action Committee, 1961 (Box A-424)
    - New Haven Alumni of Providence College, Veritus Award Dinner, 1961 (Box A-424)
    - New Haven Federation of Democratic Women's Clubs, 1962 (Box A-424)
    - New Haven Probus Club, 1962 (Box A-424)
    - New Haven Railroad, 1965 (Box A-424)
    - New Haven Railroad, 1965 (Box A-424)
    - New Haven Railroad, 1965 (Box A-424)
    - Newington Children's Hospital, 1967 (Box A-424)
    - New London Service Clubs, 1966 (Box A-424)
    - New London Service Clubs, 1962 (Box A-424)
    - Newspaper Editors, New England Society, 1964 (Box A-424)
    - North Branford High School, 1965 (Box A-424)
    - North Canaan Dedication of Sam Eddy Field, 1962 (Box A-424)
    - North Grosvenor Dale, 25th Anniversary of Community Fire Co., 1963 (Box A-424)
    - Northeastern States Boating Administrators Conference, 1966 (Box A-424)
    - Northwestern Conn. Community College Dedication, Winsted, 1965 (Box A-424)
    - Norwalk Club Meeting, Norwalk Shore and Country Club, 1966 (Box A-424)
    - Norwalk Industrial Management Club, 1962 (Box A-424)
    - Norwich - Dedication of Harry Schwartz Manor Housing Project for the Elderly, 1965 (Box A-424)
    - Norwich Area Industrial Management Club, 1965 (Box A-424)
    - Norwich Dedication of Thomas J. Kelly Junior High School, 1962 (Box A-424)
    - Norwich Hospital, Dedication of Abraham Ribicoff Research Center, 1962 (Box A-424)
    - Norwich Hospital, Dedication of Chapel, 1962 (Box A-424)
    - Archbishop O'Brien Silver Jubilee, 1965 (Box A-424)
    - Ordinance Executive Club, Army Base, Boston, 1962 (Box A-424)
    - Stanley H. Osburne Library Dedication, 1965 (Box A-424)
    - Otis Library Dedication, Norwich, 1962 (Box A-424)
    - Owls Convention, 1967 October (Box A-424)
    - Parade of Youth Scholastic Art Exhibition, 1965 (Box A-424)
    - Parent Teacher Convention, 1964 (Box A-424)
    - Parish Hill High School Chapel, Dedication, 1968 (Box A-424)
    - Parkville War Memorial, 1961 (Box A-424)
    - Remarks for Swearing in of Board of Parole, 1968 (Box A-424)
    - Partners of the Alliance Kickoff Dinner, 1965 (Box A-424)
    - Pharmaceutical Association Convention, Conn., 1965 (Box A-424)
    - Pharmaceutical Association, Conn., 1964 (Box A-424)
    - Dedication, Phelps Radiation Therapy Center, Norwich, 1968 (Box A-424)
    - Photographers Association, Hartford, 1968 (Box A-424)
    - Photographers Association Seminar, National Press, 1963 (Box A-424)
    - Pine Tree Apartments Dedication, 1967 (Box A-424)
    - Plymouth, Dedication of Hancock Brook and Northfield Brook Dams, Hancock Bridge, 1966 (Box A-424)
    - Police Academy Graduation, Conn. Chiefs of, 1965 (Box A-424)
    - Polish National Alliance 50th Anniversary of Alliance College, Stamford, 1962 (Box A-424)
    - Pomfret 250th Anniversary Celebration, 1963 (Box A-424)
    - Portland High School Dedication Ceremonies, 1961 (Box A-424)
    - Postmasters, Conn. Chapter, National Association, 1965 (Box A-424)
    - Powder House Day and 190th Anniversary, 2nd Company, Governor's Foot Guard, 1965 (Box A-424)
    - Prentice Hall Corporation, Waterford, 1961 (Box A-424)
    - Press Association, New England, 1966 (Box A-424)
    - Prentice Hall, Grand Lodge Convention, 1966 (Box A-424)
    - Probation and Parole Association, Fall Meeting, 1964 (Box A-424)
    - Probus and Unico Clubs, New Britain, 1968 (Box A-424)
    - Project Thank You, 1969 (Box A-424)
    - Providence College, 1963 (Box A-424)
    - Puerto Rican Day Dinner, 1969 (Box A-424)
    - Pulaski Day Celebration, 1964 (Box A-424)
    - Putnam, Johnston Homes for the Elderly, 1966 (Box A-425)
    - Purchasing Agents Association, Newington, 1962 (Box A-425)
    - Putnam Catholic Academy Graduation Exercises, 1969 (Box A-425)
    - Putnam, Dedication of Veterans Memorial Park and Cargill Falls Dam, 1965 (Box A-425)
    - Putnam, Dedication of New Homes for Elderly Citizens, 1963 (Box A-425)
    - Putnam, Ground Breaking for Sons of Zion Synagogue, 1965 (Box A-425)
    - Putnam, Police and Fire Building Formal Opening, 1966 (Box A-425)
    - Putnam Area Chamber of Commerce, 1965 (Box A-425)
    - Putnam High School Commencement, 1962 (Box A-425)
    - Putnam High School Reunion, 1964 (Box A-425)
    - Putnam, Ribbon Cutting Ceremony, Section of Route 52, 1965 (Box A-425)
    - Putnam Rotary Club Luncheon, 1966 (Box A-425)
    - Quinnipiac River Bridge, Interstate 91, Ground Breaking Ceremonies, 1962 (Box A-425)
    - Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, Hamden, 1962 (Box A-425)
    - Rebekah Assembly, State Convention, 1966 (Box A-425)
    - Red Cross, American, Greater Hartford Chapter, 1965 (Box A-425)
    - Red Cross High School Leadership Training Center, Montville, 1962 (Box A-425)
    - Red Mass Luncheon, Bridgeport, 1965 (Box A-425)
    - Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute Graduation Ceremonies, 1961 (Box A-425)
    - Research Commission Demonstration Vehicular Noise, Darien, 1969 (Box A-425)
    - Research in Economic Growth Conference, 1966 (Box A-425)
    - Research Symposium, Hartford, 1962 (Box A-425)
    - Revenue Task Force Organization Meeting, September, 1969 (Box A-425)
    - Mayor's Job Retraining Committee, City Hall, New Haven, 1962 (Box A-425)
    - Abe Ribicoff Appreciation Day, 1965 (Box A-425)
    - Richardson, Donald J., Colonel, Legion of Merit Award (Box A-425)
    - Ridgefield Democratic Town Committee Dinner, 1962 (Box A-425)
    - Ridgefield Library - Dedication of New Wing, 1963 (Box A-425)
    - Gens Risom Design, Incorporated, 1966 (Box A-425)
    - Road Builders" Association, Conn. Annual Meeting, 1965 (Box A-425)
    - Rockville, Franklin Park Housing Project for the Elderly, 1964 (Box A-425)
    - Rockville Area Chamber of Commerce, 1966 (Box A-425)
    - Rogers Corporation, 1964 (Box A-425)
    - Rogers Corporation, 1962 (Box A-425)
    - Rotary Club of Bridgeport, 1966 (Box A-425)
    - Danbury Rotary Club, 1964 (Box A-425)
    - Rotary Club of New Haven, 1966 (Box A-425)
    - Route 8 Opening Torrington, 1969 (Box A-425)
    - Torrington Route 8 Dedication, 1966 (Box A-425)
    - Remarks of Governor Dempsey, Route 9 Opening, Chester, 1968 (Box A-425)
    - Route 52 - Opening Ceremonies, Thompson, 1968 (Box A-425)
    - Route 72 - Ribbon Cutting Ceremony for Berlin-New Britain Section, 1962 (Box A-425)
    - Safety Commission Awards, Hartford, September, 1969 (Box A-425)
    - St. Anselm's College Commencement, 1962 (Box A-425)
    - St. Augustine School Annual Meeting, 1967 (Box A-425)
    - St. Bernard's High School Commencement, 1962 (Box A-425)
    - St. Francis Hospital Committee of 1,000, 1968 (Box A-425)
    - St. Francis Hospital Dedication of Archbishop O'Brien Building, 1961 (Box A-425)
    - St. James Episcopal Church, Danbury, 1962 (Box A-425)
    - St. Joseph College Commencement Address, 1966 (Box A-425)
    - St. Joseph College - Dedication of Gengras Center for Exceptional Children, 1965 (Box A-425)
    - St. Jude Children's Research, Danny Thomas, 1967 (Box A-425)
    - St. Jude Man of the Year Award, 1966 (Box A-425)